pcdistrict.com 2013-05-09

# Privacy Policy

All information collected at our site will be kept strictly confidential and will not be sold, reused, rented, loaned, or otherwise disclosed. Any information you give to PC District will be held with the utmost care, and will not be used in ways you have not consented to. By visiting PC District.com you are accepting our Privacy Policy, so please read carefully.

 **Personal Information**  
We do not sell, rent, loan, trade or release any personal information collected at our site, including software registration forms or e-mail lists. PC District will not under any circumstances pass on your e-mail address to other companies! We do not support unsolicited commercial e-mail! 

**Information collected on PC District.com**  
Like most web sites, PC District may collect information from its users in different ways: directly from the you, from traffic references of hosting servers and from cookies.

Information provided directly by you: when you register on PC District, we may ask you about your name, e-mail address or other personal data. You can choose not to provide this information but then you may not be able to use the full list of features of PC District.

Information from traffic references: when you visit a website, you unveil certain information about you, such as your IP address, time of visit, place from which you accessed our website. PC District stores this information. 

Information collected from cookies: in order to offer you a personalized service, PC District may use cookies to ease storing and tracking your preferences. However, the content contained is not distributed to third parties. 

PC District has advertisements served by third-party ad servers or ad networks. These third-party ad servers or ad networks use technology to send, directly to your browser, the advertisements and links that appear on PC District site. They automatically receive your IP address when this happens. They may also use other technologies (such as cookies, JavaScript, or Web Beacons) to measure the effectiveness of their advertisements and to personalize the advertising content you see. 

Advertisements served by Google, as a third party vendor, use **DART cookies**. These cookies are used to serve ads based on your visit to this site and other sites on the Internet. You may opt out of the use of the DART cookie by visiting the **Google ad and content network privacy policy.**

You need to acknowledge that, whenever you disclose information in public areas on the website that information becomes public and can easily be tracked and used by unauthorized persons. Although PC District does its best in order to protect your personal data, we cannot entirely grant you its safety. You should exercise caution when deciding to disclose your personal information. You should also know that you are the only one responsible for keeping the secret of your passwords, usernames etc. 

**Usage of information collected through the website**  
PC District uses the information collected from you for several purposes, depending on the type of data collected. Information provided directly by you: this information is used only in order to personalize the services that we offer you and to check your identity; Information from traffic references: this type of info helps us identify the parts of our site of most interest for you.  
Information collected from cookies: PC District uses cookies to help you with our services and with getting statistic information for the services improvement. Cookies allow us to save your passwords and your preferences so that you do not have to introduce them again at your next visit. 

**How we protect information collected from you**  
We value your confidentiality. PC District does not offer your personal data to third parties without your prior express consent. Any statistics that we may offer to our partners or to advertisement networks does not include any personal identifying information about any individual user.

Your access to certain services on the website is protected by a password. We advise you not to unveil this password to anyone. PC District will never ask for the password of your accounts through any kind of messages or unsolicited phone calls. We strongly advise you not to unveil your passwords to those who may ask you to. 

**Unsolicited communication**  
PC District will not use your e-mail address in order to send you any kind of unsolicited or promotional mail. It is your choice whether you decide to receive or not newsletters from us. You can always choose to unsubscribe from our newsletter services. 

If you have any questions regarding these policies, you can contact PC District by emailing [info@pcdistrict.com](mailto:info@pcdistrict.com)
